http://www.fmsni.org.uk/index.php/privacy-policy

HomeAbout FMSNIGive As You LivePrivacy PolicyContact Us
You are here....
You are here:
Home
Privacy Policy
Main Menu
HomeAbout FibromyalgiaHelpline/SupportTreatmentLocal GroupsMembershipPain ManagementFind a ConsultantGP ResourcesArticles & ResearchResourcesLinks
Give As You Live
Please support FMSNI by joining GAYL - FREE :)
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for FMSNI The privacy of our visitors to fmsni.org.uk is important to us.   We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important.
Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit this website, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Virgin), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on FMSNI.co.uk to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Belfast restaurant ads to someone in Belfast, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
Should you be unhappy with any aspect of this policy please contact us forthwith and discuss your concerns as a first measure.
© Fibromyalgia Support N. Ireland | Template by Vonfio
Site hosted with aPE computers - UK's finest!!
